question_data = {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Furby was released in 1998.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"There are 86400 seconds in a day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}